DUSTIN MOONEY

202.525.6550 | DUSTIN@MOONEY.ME | LINKEDIN.COM/IN/DUSTINMOONEY

EDUCATION

B.A. POLITICAL SCIENCE

University of Central Florida 2013

KEY SKILLS

Project Management, Marketing, Client Services, Client Experience, Microsoft Windows, Microsoft Office Suite, Apple OS, Google Workplace, Chrome OS, Linux, Adobe CC, Salesforce, SquareSpace, HTML, CSS, SEO, SEM, WordPress, HubSpot

CERTIFICATIONS

Advanced Google Analytics

Google Ads

AdMall

Analytical Forecasting

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

CONSULTANT

REBUILD Globally 2015-2018 - Remote

CAMPAIGN STAFFER

U.S. Senate Campaign 2015-2016 - Remote

AID WORKER

International Volunteer HQ 2013-2014 - Nairobi, Kenya

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST

SUMMARY

Strategic business and marketing leader with strengths in project management, client relations, client experience, branding, and digital strategy. Develop and maintain relations with key stakeholders and organizational leaders of all levels. Create materials to drive outcomes for clients and key stakeholders. *Core Competencies Include:*

Management | Marketing | Project Management | Communications

EXPERIENCE

MARKETING MANAGER / CLIENT EXPERIENCE MANAGER

Client Savvy / Remote / 2019 - 2021

Work with a team of highly skilled Client Experience (CX) professionals to achieve marketing and client success objectives. Executed a variety of marketing campaigns. Maintained relations with executives to implement and execute their CX programs.

- Generated a successful end-to-end marketing strategy. Execution included website development, podcast production, social media, content creation, among other responsibilities.
- Manage revenue of \$1M+ annually for 40+ clients. Create opportunities that drive business growth among existing clients like RTI Health and Faith.
- Directed client experience and financial consulting that led to a 14% increase in revenue for Faith Technologies while diversifying their portfolio.

DIRECTOR OF CLIENT SERVICES

3VE Marketing / Raleigh, NC / 2018 - 2019

Managed team of Account Managers who worked alongside strategists and subject matter experts to consult and execute business and marketing strategies for a wide variety of clients like Scout & Molly's and Jerry's Artarama.

- Built and led a team of Account Managers responsible for the revenue of \$1M+ annually who worked closely with subject matter experts. Services include branding, consulting, content strategy, paid, and email marketing.
- Led consulting efforts that produced a 7% increase in revenue for Action Gator Tire. Ensured revenue goals aligned with business outcomes.

MANAGER, CLIENT SUCCESS

The McClatchy Company / Raleigh, NC / 2017 - 2018

Led team of 13 Digital Strategists. Served as an intermediary between sales, production, and client success teams for this publicly traded publishing company for clients like UNC, Republic Wireless, and the Carolina Hurricanes, among others.

- Led team of Digital Strategists who managed client relationships focused on identifying needs, executing campaigns, and reporting success metrics.
- The team managed \$31M+ in annual digital revenue.

ACCOUNT DIRECTOR / SENIOR ACCOUNT MANAGER / ACCOUNT MANAGER

IZEA Worldwide / Remote / 2010 - 2017

Assumed increasing levels of accountability for the leader of influencer and content marketing software (SaaS) and services to the world's leading agencies and brands. Managed relationships with Viacom, JPMorgan, US Army, CDC, and Johnson & Johnson.

- **Project managed \$7M+ annually** for marketing initiatives on behalf of brands, advocacy organizations, and government agencies.
- Generated new business of \$1.2M+ yearly from clients like NIH and others.